<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Reportedly</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="first_paragraph">You can use shading to add a graphic design for the element to your document.Look for homes for sale in the neighborhoods you love. If you used a color under Theme Colors to apply for shading in your document.</string>
    <string name="second_paragraph">If you used a color under Theme Colors to apply for shading in your document, you can change the color of the shading and other colors in your document by applying a new theme or theme color to the major document.</string>
    <string name="third_paragraph"> Look for homes for sale in the neighborhoods you love, and make weekend open houses a regular outing during this phase. Each of those will have features that inspire you, and features that will leave you unmoved. If you used a for color under Theme Colors to apply some for shading in your document, you can change the color of the shading and other colors in your there document by applying a new theme or theme color to the major document.The works discussed in this essay share obvious similarities. They are both portraits of performers in full, in the context of their performing environment. In Indifferent, there is a sense of the subject posing for the portrait in a very festive manner which is characteristic of the Rococo period. By contrast, in Delacroix Paganini the performer seems to carry himself with a much more intrinsic purpose, perhaps enacting a more truthful value that is typical of the Romantic ideal. There is, nevertheless, a similarity in the two poses that suggests motion, as both performers seem to be caught in mid movement. This dynamic quality was not typical of the other art movements prior to or during the 18th century, where portraits tended to depict people in staid, sober poses.Before you draw a single line, consult an architect, or buy that cool new software application that will do it all, consider your dreams. At the very beginning of this process, it not about board feet or setbacks or even floor plans. It about how you define your desires</string>
    <string-array name="prflPic">
        <item >Take Picture</item>
        <item >From Gallery</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>